joomlavi.com 2016-11-26

# Privacy Policy

**COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

**Personally identifiable data:**

Data that identifies or can be used to identify user or user’s personal information may include your name, address, email address, User IP address( in case that it has not been deleted, clipped or anonymized) and your phone number etc…. We never collect personally identifiable information without your consent. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction. Joomlavi collects personally identifiable information that can be divided into the following categories:

Joomlavi Product Registration Information:  When ordering products or services on our site, you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information which is necessary to conclude the transaction, and for applicable products, to be eligible to receive technical support.  
Credit Card Information: If you use a credit card to purchase our products via this Site, your name as it appears on the credit card, the credit card number, expiration date and billing address will be encrypted as it passes over the Internet. Joomlavi does not record or keep your credit card information for online credit-card transactions; rather such information is simply passed through to our contracted payment processing vendor. Joomlavi may access such information through the payment processing company, but does not do so except to process refunds or adjustments and to the extent necessary in the event of nonpayment or disputed payments, or as may be necessary for Joomlavi compliance, in Joomlavi discretion, with applicable law.  
Technical Support: If you request technical support online, we will ask you for information necessary to complete the transaction such as your name, email address and information about your computer hardware, software, and the nature of the problem you are experiencing. In the course of providing support, your data may be transmitted to service providers that are under contract to Joomlavi and have agreed to abide by the provisions of this privacy policy. Such transmissions of your data are encrypted and secure.  
Partner Application: If you request participation in the partner program online, we will ask you for information necessary to complete the transaction such as company name, email address, and company profile.

**Non-personal Data:**[Lam web chuan SEO](http://www.jpwebseo.com/)

Like most websites, we gather statistical and other analytical information collected on an aggregate basis of all visitors to our website. This non-personal information consist of data that cannot be used to identify or contact you such as demographic information regarding like user IP addresses where they have been clipped or anonymised, browser types and other anonymous statistical information involving the use of our website.

**EMAIL COMMUNICATION**[academy toeic](http://leanhtien.net/download/sach-toeic/toeic-academyu-truc-schema)

Email: With your permission, Joomlavi will send you communications, including informative emails/newsletters about product upgrades, product updates, new products, and services. These communications provide you with special offers that may be of interest to you. Joomlavi uses a third-party program of outbound email technology to send email from our servers and does not collect information about you but does collect requests to unsubscribe.  
Site Functionality  
Cookies: A "cookie" is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Site. Once you close your browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Site, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our Site. You may still use our Site if you reject the cookie. The only drawback to this is that you will be limited in some areas of our Site. For example, you will not be able to use certain features of our forum or other parts of the Site that offer customized settings.  
Log Files: We (Joomlavi and/or our contracted web analytics provider(s)) do keep track of the domains from which you access our Site and Services on the World Wide Web, and may log IP addresses or other identifiers for statistical purposes. We do this to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use to identify and analyze trends and the results of our marketing efforts, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site and Services, and analyze users' movements. We may periodically share aggregate demographic information with our business partners. IP addresses and other identifiers are not linked to personally identifiable information.  
Links: This Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Joomlavi are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Site.  
Newsletter: If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.[cach redirect 404](http://www.jpwebseo.com/cach-redirect-trang-404-ve-home-page-trong-wordpress)

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

All information gathered on our site is stored and maintained in secure facilities that limit to access to authorized personnel only. In addition, internal security provides that this information is coded with restricted access, and our servers are kept in a secure, locked environment that limits access to authorized personnel only. All Joomlavi employees are briefed about the company's privacy and security policies on a regular basis. Our site is regularly tested for security breaches to ensure that all information collected is secure from unauthorized viewing.

**CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If your personal information changes (eg. Name, address, postal code, telephone number, etc.) or you no longer desire our services, we will endeavor to provide the way to correct, update or remove this information.
